### MeetMatch - Privacy Policy

This document provides the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) that governs how we, MeetMatch (“MeetMatch”, “we”, “our” or “us”), use Personal Information (as defined below) which we collect, receive and store about individuals and/or companies in connection with the use of: (i) the website https://www.meetmatch.biz/, and any other website that we operate (each, together with its sub-domains, content and services, a “Site”); and (ii) the MeetMatch web and mobile software application, and any other software application, that we license (each individually, and collectively, the “Software”). The Site and the App are individually and collectively referred to herein as the “Services”.

**1\. Introduction.** We have implemented this Privacy Policy because your privacy, and the privacy of other users, is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Information is collected and used in connection with the Services. “Personal Information” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a personal profile, an email address or other contact information.

**2\. Terms of Use.** This Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms of Use which is available at \[[reg.meetmatch.biz/files/terms.html](https://reg.meetmatch.biz/files/terms.html)\] (“Terms”). Any capitalized but undefined term in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given to it in the Terms.

**3\. Consent and Modification.** By using the Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our collection, processing and sharing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or otherwise use the Services. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such change will be effective ten (10) days following posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and/or Software, and your continued use of the Services thereafter means that you accept those changes.

**4\. What Personal Information We Collect and How We Collect It.** We do not currently require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to general information available on the Site and/or Software. But, we do receive and/or collect Personal Information from you in the following ways:

**4.1. Account.** In order to use certain services that we offer via the Site and/or Software, you may be required to create an account (“Account”). We may offer different options to create an Account, including:

> (a) Online Registration Form: You may choose to complete and submit an online registration form. You will be asked to provide us with certain mandatory information such as your name and email address.
> 
> (b) Third Party Accounts: You may choose to create an Account by clicking on a ‘connect’ or ‘sign-in’ button that we may display on the Site and/or Software for a designated third party website or service (each a “Third Party Account”), including but not limited to, LinkedIn, Facebook or Twitter. Doing so will enable you to link your Service Account and your Third Party Account. If you choose this option, then you will be required to approve the connection as well as the types of information (which may include Personal Information) that we will obtain from your Third Party Account and the types of activities that we may perform in connection with your \`Third Party Account. Please note that in order to use this option, you will need to have, and may need to be signed-in to, an existing Third Party Account.

Regardless of which method you choose to register your Account, we may send an email to your nominated email address to instruct you how to confirm your registration. You may also choose to provide further information, such as company you work for and specific topics you are currently interested in.

**4.2. ‘Contact Us’ Information.** If you send us a “Contact Us” request, whether by submitting an online form that we make available or by sending an email to an email address that we display, you may be required to provide us with certain information, such as your name and email address.

**4.3. Share with Friends Service.** The Site and/or Software may enable you to invite your friends to use our Services by sending them an invitation email or message. You may do so by: (i) using the Site and/or Software to send or post an invitation message via your Third Party Account; and/or (ii) using the Site and/or Software to send an invitation email to your friend’s external email address (for example, a Gmail address). If you send or post an invitation message, we may collect Personal Information about the recipient such as their email address or their third party website account user name and id.

**4.4. Purchases.** The Site and/or Software may include the option to purchase certain products or services from us. If you choose to make a purchase we will require sufficient information from you to complete the transaction. This information is fully handled by our sub-processor for payment, Mollie BV. Such information could include a credit card number and related account and billing information, invoice related information, and other data required to process the order. We may also update such data should you grant us permission to bill you or your credit card for recurring charges, such as monthly or other types of periodic payments. We may use the tools, software or services of third-party service providers to process transactions on our behalf, in which case you acknowledge and agree to review and be bound by the terms of use and privacy policy of said third-party service provider.

**4.5. Log Files.** We may make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the Services, track user’s movement around the Services, and gather demographic information.

**4.6. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.** Our Services may utilize “cookies”, anonymous identifiers and other tracking technologies in order for us to provide our Services and present you with information that is customized for you. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about activity on the Services. Certain cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information, such as an IP address, previously indicated by a user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.

**4.7. Mobile Device Data.** We may collect limited information from your mobile device in order to provide the Software. Such information may include your mobile device type, mobile device id, and date and time stamps of Software use. In addition, we may deploy tracking technologies within the Software to help us gather aggregate statistics.

**5\. Publicly Available Information.** Your Public Profile and any publicly available content that you post on or via the Services (“User Submissions”) may be publicly available to other users of the Services, and may also be accessed and used by people of the Services. For instance, if you view another user’s profile or ‘like’ a certain event within the Services, such information can be viewed by others. The notices and tools that we provide on the Services should help inform you which information will be made publicly available. If you publish your contact information in any User Submissions or as part of your Public Profile, you may receive unsolicited messages from other users of the Services or the public. We therefore encourage you to only post information that you are sure you want to be accessible to anyone.

**6\. The Way We Use Personal Information.** If you submit or we collect Personal Information through the Services, then we may use such Personal Information in the following ways:

6.1. We will use your Personal Information to provide and improve our Services, to contact you in connection with the Services and certain programs or offerings that you may have registered for, and to identify and authenticate your access to the parts of the Services that you are authorized to access.

6.2. We may use your designated email address to: (i) send you updates or news regarding the Services and our products; (ii) respond to a “Contact Us” or administrative request (for example, to change your password); (iii) send you suggested events, based on events your Third Party Account connections and friendships are attending; and/or (iv) send you ads and related content and information for marketing or promotional purposes.

6.3. If you choose to send your friend an invitation email or message we will use the contact information that you provide, or make available, to automatically send your friend an invitation email or message. Your name and email address may be included in the invitation email or message. You can turn off any of these messages at any time.

6.4. We may share your Personal Information, Anonymous Information (as defined below) and other statistical and analytical information to the event organizers of the events which you have purchased tickets to (“Event Organizers”), for the purpose of providing you with the Services. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We require that the Event Organizers agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy. Event Organizers may also use your designated email address to send you updates or news regarding the events you are attending.

6.5. We may transfer your Personal Information to our subsidiaries for the purpose of storing or processing such information on our behalf. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. These subsidiairies conform to this same Privacy Policy.

6.6. We have the right to disclose some of the Personal Information to:

* Mailchimp service to send you email with an invitation for the Event and/or the Community- this purpose requires disclosure of your email address, your first and last name, your job title, the name of a company/organization you work for, your call-to-action URL with token that signs you in for the Event and/or the Community (such token works only for two days from the moment of its creation);
* OVH Hosting Services to host your (User's) files - this purpose requires disclosure of your profile picture, logo of the Event and/or the Community you take/took part in, pictures of meeting points of the Event and/or the Community you take/took part in;
* Bugsnag, Inc. to possibly follow up errors and warnings which you encounter during usage of our solutions- this purpose requires exchange of your IP address and browser info;

For certain events, this list also includes:

* Twilio, Inc. - this cooperation requires disclosure of your (User's) phone number, list of meetings, call-to-action URL with token that works only for two days from the moment of its creation - thanks to it you will be able to receive a text message (SMS) with an overview of the meetings and URL to the web app, if this is applicable for the event you participate in;
* Crisp, for providing an in-app helpdesk- this purpose requires your name, the event you participate in and your browser info;
* Mollie, for allowing you to pay e.g. for tickets. The key information like credit card info is fully handled by Mollie, in accordance with ongoing Privacy guide lines;

6.7. We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Services if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our Terms, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of MeetMatch, our users, yourself or the public.

**7\. Use of Anonymous Information.** We may use Anonymous Information or disclose it to third party service providers in order to improve our Services and enhance your experience with the Services. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners. “Anonymous Information” means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of our Services.

**8\. Opting Out.** You may choose not to receive future promotional, advertising or other Services-related emails from us by replying 'unsubscribe' to each email that we send. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving the foregoing emails, we may still send you a response to any “Contact Us” request as well as administrative emails (for example, in connection with a password reset request) that are necessary to facilitate your use of the Services.

**9\. Choice.** At all times, you may choose whether or not to provide or disclose Personal Information. If you choose not to provide mandatory Personal Information, you may still visit parts of the Services but you may be unable to access certain options, programs, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

**10\. Access/Accuracy.** To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate Personal Information. If you would like to delete or correct any of your other Personal Information that we may be storing, you may use the tools that we make available on the Services or you may submit an access request by sending an email to support@meetmatch.biz. Your email should include adequate details of your request.

**11\. Links to and Interaction with Third Party Products.** The Services may enable you to interact with or contain links to your Third Party Account and other third party websites, mobile software applications and services that are not owned or controlled by us (each a “Third Party Service”). We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these Third Party Services. Please be aware that the Third Party Services may collect Personal Information from you. Accordingly, we encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each Third Party Service that you choose to use or interact with.

**12\. Children’s Privacy.** The Services are not structured to attract children under the age of 13 years. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at support@meetmatch.biz.

**13\. Security.** The security of Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards, including the use of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards, to protect the Personal Information submitted to us. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or confidentiality. If you have any questions about security on the Service, you can contact us at support@meetmatch.biz.

**14\. Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy.** In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer or assign Personal Information in connection with the foregoing events.

**15\. Commitment.** We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and we are constantly evolving our Service to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or your Personal Information that we may be storing and using, please contact us at support@meetmatch.biz.

Last updated: August 2021
